Today and time, I'm two of those in location by Ryan Orkitt.
No, by...
James?
Okay.
Oh, no wait, Martin.
I can't believe you.
I saw Mark walking in, I thought.
He knows this is going to pickle ball.
He did it.
I just arrived.
I was here.
I saw him walking, I thought he was going to spit you on the spot.
I thought he was going to spit you on the spot.
I'm sorry.
And the father, we have a great opportunity for all of you.
We have to be thankful for all of you in this community.
We have much.
It's a father we can get to pray and work.
Ask God now for wisdom and knowledge and his leaders.
If they would seek to honor you and honor the people who are just community.
If all of them did, and we can pray and work all of the things that happen as a result.
Did you just make it happen?
Ryan, would you like to pledge?
I pledge to be in the state of the flag.
The United States of America.
And to the Republic for which it stands, one nation, under God.
In the middle of the liberty that is for all.
Thank you, Ryan.
Thank you, Mark.
Thank you.
Item three is public input.
Don't discuss the personal appearances.
Anyone in the nine twist to address the authorities or any of the agenda items?
Item four or excuse me.
Item five is percentage in the staff.
It's recommending nine or six to ready for the consent agenda.
I'm going to ask the full item.
Any of this doesn't need to discuss for a moment.
So that leaves item six and seven with your claims and minutes.
Do we have a motion to approve?
Item six and seven.
Seven.
And I'll second that roll call please.
Or can.
Should I?
Davis.
All right.
Weston.
Aye.
Okay.
And then item eight, I just asked to be pulled out.
So either jail or being can explain why we're approving this budget before we prove the master budget.
And I understand there's an answer for that.
But I just wanted to, because I asked it yesterday, I wanted to, the rest of the council
of the moment.
By saying that to you, the council has to approve the budget within seven days before the
start of the next fiscal year, the trust has to approve an estimate.
So I have sent the budget to every trust, you really said to say, there's a much, it can
be two numbers.
You're in what we're going to make and here's what we're going to spend, but I do, you know,
what we're going to do.
We'll do a little bit of that.
But every trust needs to approve their own budget.
And when we look at the master budget, the MSUA was part of that.
We just didn't talk about it and really separately too much, but it was part of that, what
we saw.
Okay.
Actually, it's a significant part.
Right.
It's a significant part.
So thank you, Jill.
I'll make a motion to approve item eight.
Do we have a second?
Yes.
Go call please.
So, aye.
Davis.
All right.
Western.
Thank you.
Item nine.
And now is the knowledge permit number,
long numbers and letters for,
for the, I'm gonna do EQ for West Central Waterway
from D to A.
This is just a requirement to DQ makes it
and it's gonna be acknowledged that we have to permit.
Can I put the next meeting
so where's their knowledge that we have to permit
for that portion of West Central.
And it's just a project we talked about a few weeks ago.
That was essential.
Okay, this is a, this is the smallest blowpiece
from the D to H people.
That's a lotta hole, central, ab and N.
We can do a motion to approve of that.
I need it for anything.
Okay.
I'll just take knowledge.
And it has to be done.
Senator acknowledged.
Thank you.
Item 10 is of the new business.
Did you business anyone?
Item 11 is staff reports, though,
into the practice, staff available 30 questions.
Item 12 is trustee community announcements.
I would like to acknowledge the two banks that
made a considerable effort as we were working with our utility customers.
They were accepting credit cards with no fee to the consumer.
And that was Welch, an over the phone and first national.
And so we appreciate the help that they gave us,
getting through that time.
Since we're talking about the MSU-AB.
Is there any updates on the payments?
Yes.
Some stuff.
I got some notes.
I was going to do it under managers comments,
but I'd be happy to do it now.
Heather has been doing a phenomenal job.
And we're getting people coming in right now.
We've had lines of people.
Thank goodness.
Which is what we expected people waiting to the last minute.
But as it stands right now, we have about two,
we're down to about 295 accounts.
But we think that as we go on,
that number will continue to drop down.
The cycle four, which is the first cycle that we'll be experiencing,
which was shut off, and that's going to be on June 9.
Right now we're at a total of 127.
But of course, we still have to the end of this week for people to bring that number down.
We hope that as we talk about this publicly,
I really appreciate the news record.
They did a great article explaining how this works.
We hope that number will continue to go down.
Now, let's see, that is the cycle that's coming up.
I think right now we have on cycle one,
which would be the next one is 76.
Cycle two, we have 64 and cycle three, one up one.
So probably as those numbers will start coming down.
Now, at our last meeting, we set you an email as a follow-up,
but I'll just go ahead and say it for the record as well.
You really want to make sure that we went the extra mile.
The extra mile, extra mile actually.
And we have a process right now that this coming Thursday for the first time
toward the end of the day, Heather will...
basically run off the number of, of this number of houses or businesses.
There are still a few left, but most of the businesses are being taken care of.
We'll do that Thursday, first thing Friday morning, Kevin, his cruise, which would be our
statement cruise, which would be our parks cruise and all that.
Before they go to work, they're going to ditty those up and put them on the doors.
And that's going to be first thing Friday morning.
We would not even be doing the cut-offs until Tuesday.
So that way, they're on the door.
All day Friday, through the weekend, all day Monday, it's getting everybody that last chance
before we have to start shutting things down.
So we hope that people will see that.
We'll hear the articles.
We'll hear the word of mouth.
We've been putting things on Facebook.
We've been putting things on other social media and our website.
I think it's what we've expected that we, I'm sure we're going to have cut-offs.
I'm not saying you won't have any at all.
But we hope we're starting to little that down.
We're starting to see progress.
So we're keeping our fingers cutting off.
Any questions for Dean Ornette?
Well, as of from last Tuesday, I forgot what I was going to say.
We're going to have four hundred four hundred four hundred four hundred.
So we went down over it.
Yeah.
One is considerable.
We're over at 120 and 160 and 70.
Four twenty-two.
Oh, we've gone down about nine.
Oh, I have to.
Okay.
Four twenty-two.
Yeah.
Four three-four.
Okay.
Well, at hundred twenty-seven number still a big scary number.
Hopefully we'll see a lot of people come.
I think a lot of people are going to last minute.
And again, I really do want to thank the news record because that.
I think that article is really very accurate.
A lot of people catch on from the air.
Some of them are trying to do.
I don't know.
The likelihood that they would repeat that before we cycle.
There was some version of that.
We were on this reminder that we can work with you and see if we could take a help
to switch.
Yeah.
Of course.
We'll continue to do things on social media too.
I don't have 13 is a German.
Do we have a motion to join the S.J. meeting?
Yes.
Second.
We'll call.
Do you miss?
All right.